It's another Paradise video but this one is not about pants as the one I'm wearing here but
about jumpsuits because Paradise released two jumpsuits one in this four-bedder fabric and
one in activewear fabric and I'm going to show them to you today and style them so let's go
all right let me put it on
So as with the leggings and the pants we have this V shape here in the back so they took
over their pants design here and we also have a different cut here in the front than most
leggings because we have some extra seams here and also some decorative seams here which
makes it a bit more interesting design wise and I think almost looks like some fake corset
lines which I really like.
So I'm wearing size small and I have to say the four leather version I think runs a bit
small.
The fabric version is true to size but here I'd recommend evened out size up and I think
with my 173 centimeters I'm at the maximum height so I would recommend this
for people who are a bit shorter than me because it does have a lot of tension
especially here in the back it's a little bit too short it's not that
uncomfortable so I can still wear it but I already tried the other one I could
say it's longer which is more comfortable for me I put on some thigh
high boots from Furniture Berlin and it's now like a two in one jumpsuit because
it's still the short leg jumpsuit here but with the boots you can't really tell
anymore because they're so high so now it looks just like a long leg jumpsuit
basically and I put a belt on it and we'll also add a leather jacket
I think it's super cool that the belt buckle here is visible in the cutout area of the jacket
like it was made for it and of course
it's a really nice look kind of like it closing the zipper and also a nice look
normally I like zipper open always better but I think this time it's zipper closed for me
and you can tell me in the comments if you like zipper open or zipper closed
okay once again the full body look with the jacket
and now I will change into the next one the activewear fabric jumpsuit is just so
comfy because the fabric is really really stretchy and
Really soft if you already own paradise sportswear then you should know it is the same
it's also
Since it's so stretchy it runs slightly bigger so I recommend if
When in doubt size down
Because you can already see it's a bit loose here, so it's really long for me with the length no problem
really really comfortable
and also like perfect to chill on the couch for example because it's so comfy
but I think I can also pair it with a leather jacket for example for a cool look
I'm already wearing my buffaloes
so let me check
yeah as I thought it looks sporty but also grungy with the jacket and the boots
so it's almost giving like skater vibes
or some like, I don't know,
sportive cool vibes.
I like it.
I like the look.
I like that it's really, really comfy basic,
which you can pimp with, for example,
leather jacket or boots,
but also you can wear the belt I've shown before
and the other leather jacket and boots too.
So yeah, it's pretty versatile.
And I think
it's a look.
Of course, closing this one too.
Also without a jacket again.
Alright, I think I prefer the look with the four-leather jumpsuit though and for a nice Sunday chill this one.
But yeah, that was it for today.
I hope you enjoyed this one. I do have a Paradise discount code, so if you want to order the jumpsuits,
you can get some percent off. You can find everything down in the description text.
And my discount code also counts for all the new items like the latest sports collection
or these jumpsuits, the heels, the dresses. Just have a look at the Paradise page and I hope you're
you having a nice day. I will see you in the next video. Thanks for sticking around. Bye.